We're very proud that sharing the vision for the decentral web has allowed us to attract a lot of talented people.
Actually from all over the world like people moved over from South Africa, from the US in order to join the team
and build with us this vision for Polkadot and the decentral web going forward so
parts of the team are focused on the interoperability right now, some of the team are focused on the scalability.
There's also a smaller team working on the
interfaces so that actually people can easily going forward interact with the technology that we're building.
So when we launch in 2019 really that's just the start for us so
there's a whole range of other technologies that we're working on already like
work on privacy that's going to continue after the launch and be integrated into Polkadot.
So yeah we are really committed to build our Polkadot as part of the future decentralized web and
continuing the work after the launch.